BRIAN HE

0452 075 051 | <u>brian.he3@gmail.com</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/brian-he-b52780164</u> | Sydney, Australia

PROFILE

Highly motivated and conscientious professional services specialist with over three years of experience in delivering value for public clients. Versatile skill set with proven track record in performing analytics, sales and open communication. Dedicated to continuous learning and ongoing self-development, seeking to provide viable solutions for the most complex problems.

EDUCATION

Coder Academy

Ultimo, Sydney, NSW

Diploma of Information Technology (Higher Education)

October 2020 - present

Chartered Accountants Australia New Zealand

Graduate Diploma of Chartered Accounting

Sydney, NSW

September 2018 – June 2020

University of New South Wales

Kensington, NSW

Bachelor of Commerce in Accounting and Finance

March 2014 - November 2017

• WAM: 71.895

• RG146 Tier 1 Compliant

Sydney Boys High School

Surry Hills, NSW

Higher School Certificate

January 2008 - November 2013

- 93.2 ATAR
- Distinguished Achievers List 2013 Higher School Certificate

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Minus Three

Sydney NSW

Co-Founder

July 2020 - present

- Co-founding a company that specializes in fashion for the shorter man
- Conducting major strategic, marketing, operational and financial decisions within the company

Grant Thornton Australia

Kent Street, Sydney NSW

Associate – Audit & Assurance

April 2018 – June 2020

- Conducting audits and preparing financial statements for small and medium sized business, listed companies and not-for-profit entities
- Establishing rapport with client finance teams and senior management personnel through the audit engagement
- Perform analytical and risk assessment procedures over the financial statements of clients
- Worked closely with a team of junior staff whilst aiding them in the progression of their knowledge and careers and providing internal training sessions

Grant Thornton Australia

Summer Vacationer - Audit & Assurance

Kent Street, Sydney NSW January 2017 – February 2017

Macquarie Gordon & Co.

Elizabeth Street, Sydney NSW

Intermediate Accountant – Corporate Insolvency

August 2016 - December 2016

- Conducting investigations and recoveries against companies for Insolvent Trading, Uncommercial Transactions and Voidable Transactions
- Assisting the Liquidator and a team of senior staff in the process of corporate Administrations

Hall Chadwick Chartered Accountants

Park Street, Sydney NSW

Cadet – Corporate Insolvency

April 2015 - March 2016

- Liaising with various external parties such as ASIC, company directors, creditors, solicitors and banks throughout a company's Administration process
- Facilitating Liquidation, Receivership and Voluntary Administration processes in accordance with the Corporations Act 2001

Insport

Drummovne NSW

Sales Team Member April 2017 - June 2018

Tutoring for Excellence

Bondi Junction NSW Personal Tutor January 2015 – April 2015

KFC Sydney Central Plaza

Team Member

Pitt St, Sydney NSW

February 2014 – April 2015

SKILLS, ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

Languages

- Conversational proficiency in Mandarin
- Conversational proficiency in Cantonese

Technical Skills

- Basic Proficiency in Python
- Advanced Proficiency in MYOB, Xero, Netsuite and Reckon accounting systems

Activities

- Homebush OzTag Mixed Team member
- Centennial Parkland Mixed Netball team member
- Member at Fit'n Fast gym

Interests

- 7th Grade AMEB clarinet
- 3rd Grade AMEB Musicianship
- Founder of jersey business "Swifte Apparel"